[
    {
        "que_id": "1",
        "question": "Welcome to our Health Insurance Planning System! To ensure I provide you with the best health insurance plan, I'll need some information. Your privacy is important, and all your information will be handled confidentially. Let's get started!.Firstly what is your name?",
        "answer": "Nisarg",
        "tag": "name",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "2",
        "question": "Okay Now, age, the age is a crucial factor in tailoring the best health insurance plan for you.Can you please tell me what is your age?",
        "answer": 22,
        "tag": "age",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "3",
        "question": "Great, thank you. Now, could you share your current weight in pounds?",
        "answer": 72,
        "tag": "weight",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "4",
        "question": "Perfect. Next, can you tell me the city where you currently reside?",
        "answer": "Mumbai",
        "tag": "city",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "5",
        "question": "Excellent. And what is your gender?",
        "answer": "male",
        "tag": "gender",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "6",
        "question": "Thank you. Now, could you share a bit about your occupation or job?",
        "answer": "Software Engineer",
        "tag": "job",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "7",
        "question": "Great to know. Moving on, could you please share the number of family members you'd like to include in the plan?",
        "answer": 5,
        "tag": "members",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "8",
        "question": "Perfect. Now, are there any hereditary diseases or medical conditions that run in your family that we should be aware of?",
        "answer": "No Diseases",
        "tag": "dieces",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "9",
        "question": "Thank you for providing that information. Next, do you smoke?please say yes or no",
        "answer": "no ",
        "tag": "smoke",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "10",
        "question": "Now, could you please share your blood pressure levels in digits?",
        "answer": 82,
        "tag": "bp",
        "trial": 0
    },
    {
        "que_id": "11",
        "question": "Thank you for sharing that. Lastly, do you engage in regular exercise?please say yes or no",
        "answer": "yes",
        "tag": "exercise",
        "trial": 0
    }
]